我们为你提供了一个图标库，请看下边的链接，
We're providing you with an asset drop, view the link below,
从这儿你可以下载不同的图片并把它们添加到你的app中。
so that you can download the images and include them in
解压图标库后，
the app. When we open up the assets ZIP file, we
可以看到，我们为不同的分辨率提供了不同的图标大小。
see that the same icon is provided at different sizes for
drawable MDPI文件夹中的图片
different resolutions. In the drawable MDPI folder, we see the assets
将被用于MDPI分辨率的设备。 而drawable HDPI
that will be used on an MDPI device. In the drawable
文件夹中的图片则会被用于HDPI分辨率的设备。
HDPI folder, we see the assets that will be used on
以此类推。
an HDPI device. And the same goes for the other folders.
在res目录下，把下载好的内容中的所有目录
Under the res directory copy over all the asset
拷贝过来。单击时可以预览图片，
folders provided in the download. Clicking on an image shows
同时查看它的大小及像素值。
a preview of it and the size and pixels
这个时候，你也可以将旧的
is also shown. At this time you can also remove
占位图标移除了。注意，新的启动图标
the old placeholder ic launcher icons. Our new launcher
位于mipmap文件夹中。这些文件夹不同于
icons are located in mipmap folders. These are distinct folders
drawable文件夹。如果你为特定的
from the drawable folders. If you build an APK
目标屏幕分辨率打了个APK，比如 HDPI分辨率，那么，安卓资源打包工具，
for a target screen resolution like HDPI, the Android asset
即AAPT，将会精简掉其他分辨率的drawables文件。
packaging tool, AAPT, can strip out the drawables for other resolutions
但是如果是在mipmap文件夹中，
that you don't need. But if it's in the mipmap folders,
那么这些资源会被保留下来，不管是什么目标分辨率。
then these assets will stay in the APK regardless of the
那么问题就来了，我们什么时候才需要使用
target resolution. But when would you need an image at a
那些分辨率与屏幕分辨率不同的图标呢？
resolution different than the resolution of the device? Well, one example
那就是桌面启动图标！这是个很好的例子。它控制着手机主屏幕以及
is the Android launcher app, which controls the home screen as
整个应用商店。桌面启动图标
well as the All App store. The launcher app won't use
没有使用当前设备的分辨率，而是
the icon at the current density of the device, but rather
使用了精度更高的分辨率。例如，对于XXHDPI分辨率的设备，
pulls a icon for the next highest resolution up. For an XXHDPI device like the
Nexus 5，正常情况下，图标会默认从
Nexus 5, normally the assets will be pulled
drawable XXHDPI文件夹中提取。然而，在这种情况下，
from the drawable XXHDPI folder. However, in this
我们会使用mipmap文件夹下分辨率为XXXHDPI
case the launcher icon will pull the XXXHDPI
的图标。
version of the launcher icon. That will make
这样的大图标会更加鲜亮的显示在
the larger app icons appear sharper on the
众多图标之中。   由于提取图标的位置改变了，我们也需要
all apps screen. In the code replace @drawable/ic_launcher
将代码中的 @drawable/ic_launcher替换为@mipmap/ic_launcher。
with @mipmap/ic_launcher because of the new location of the icons.
对于其他图标，请修改预报列表中的
For the rest of the icons modify the forecast list
以及详细视图处，来显示正确的天气图标，而不是占位图。
and the details screen to display the right weather icon
参考下方的辅助提示。
instead of the placeholder one. See the hints below in
使用下面的代码片段中，提供的辅助函数，
the instructor notes. Using the helper functions we've provided in
来帮助你把天气情况的代码映射到
the gist below, you can map the weather condition code
你需要的图标上。到此为止，看看手机屏幕，
to the icon that you'll need. This is what the
这就是我们的app现在应该呈现出来的样子。
app should look like when you're done with this step.
注意，这里有两种类型的天气图标
Note that there are two types of each weather
一种是灰色，另一种是彩色。
icon, a gray icon and a colored art image.
在一周得天气列表中，我们使用灰色图标。
In the main forecast list we'll be using the
而显示今天天气的部分，我们使用彩色的图标。
gray icon. However, for the today layout, we'll use the
当你点击进入，查看任何一天天气的详细信息时，
colored icon. When you go inside the detail activity,
你看到的图标也会是彩色的。这时
you'll also use the colored icon. At this time,
如果你是采用硬编码方式将图片信息写入到layout的xml文件中的话
you can also remove any images you hard coded
你大可以将他们删除掉，因为这些部分可以被自动填充（在代码中更新填充）。
into the layout XML, because they'll be populated dynamically now.